MARY PRISILLA R

Digital Engagement manager

CONTACT

8870962287 maryprisillapkt@gmail.com

EDUCATION

B.E MECHATRONICS ENGINEERING

Anna University

2014-2018

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

St isabel Higher Secondary school

State Board - SSLC April 2012

St isabel Higher Secondary school
State Board - HSC March 2014

SKILLS

Content Writing
poster Design
MS Office
Auto cad

C,C++

REFERENCES

Mr.Prem

9500666671

Manchester Honda -GM

SUMMARY

A passionate digital manager with over 4 years 8 months experience in Automobile industry as a Service advisor, customer Experience manager & Digital manager .To seek an opportunity to serve a company where my knowledge and skills are well utilized for the development of the organization and also for my career growth.

WORK EXPERIENCE

DIGITAL ENGAGEMENT MANAGER MAHINDRA CAI

Really Great Company

2022- Present

- Need to handle social media platforms ,websites and GMB page and improve the High no's of Leads conversion & positive Followers
- Create social media creatives ,posters ,handbills
- · Developed visual style guide
- Major role customer experience handling
- Improve to convert quality leads using Hyperlocal leads vendor leads

SERVICE ADVISOR SGA SKODA

Really Great Company

2021 - 2022

- receiving the customer, responding their queries, finding out the work, scheduling vehicles for the service, educating technician, final quality inspection and full fledging customer's desires and delivering the vehicle to the customer.
- need to Achieve Revenue Based Goals
- Customer Delighting Plays a vital Role

SERVICE ADVISOR RAMANI AUTOMOBILE PVT LTD - MANCHESTER HONDA

Really Great Company

2018 - 2021

- receiving the customer, responding their queries, finding out the
 work, scheduling vehicles for the service, educating technician, final
 quality inspection and full fledging customer's desires and delivering
 the vehicle to the customer.
- need to Achieve Revenue Based Goals
- Customer Delighting Plays a vital Role

PROJECT PROFILE:

Title: Control and Monitoring Textile Waste Water Using SCADA, 2018

Mission to accomplish an environment friendly industrial Waste

water system.

Framing an innovative concept which could automatically regulate toxicity in the waste waterDesign and Fabrication of Semi-Automated Drainage Cleaning System.

An aim to segregate solid waste from municipal drainage system by creating a semi-automated fabrication which could separate solid by fetching process.

INDUSTRIAL EXPOSURE:

Undergone IN -PLANT Training in AMBAL AUTO, Coimbatore.

TECHNICAL EXPERIENCE:

DEM Training - Bangalore

Participated in one-day PLC workshop, Coimbatore.

Completed HSAS Training from HONDA, Chennai.

Completed H- SMART Training from

HONDA, Chennai

DECLARATION:

I do solemnly declare that the above furnished details are true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Date:	Sincerely
Place:	(R.Mary Prisilla)